[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
[Episode 9]
I'll draw Zhou Yang.
Or maybe I'll draw you.
You love this sofa bed so much.
You don't even want to sleep with me.
Your right hand is seriously injured.
There might be permanent aftereffects.
It will affect your daily life.
Please be mentally prepared.
What's wrong?
What are you doing?
Oh. I... I'm just cleaning up.
Why are you crying?
Oh.
Maybe I slept too much this afternoon.
I'm fine.
It hurts?
The injury on my hand is probably still recovering.
It'll be fine once it heals.
It doesn't matter if it never fully heals.
At worst, I'll just stop painting.
I'll find another job then.
Like insurance or sales.
Maybe I'll even make more money.
You can't hold a brush?
Yeah.
I'm here for you.
Don't worry.
I'll be okay.
Keep it up, Shen Mo.
You can do this.
I can't be a burden to Zhou Yang.
- Hello. - And you are?
I'm the one who contacted you online.
I'm here to apply for the art teacher job.
Did you bring your resume?
[Resume] [Shen Mo]
Shen Mo.
Your resume is very impressive.
Not at all.
Have you been training since you were a kid?
I've been painting since I was little.
I've also been working part-time since I started college.
So, I have quite a bit of experience.
Please take a look at my works.
Wow.
These are really good.
You're professionally trained and draw so well.
Say, what brought you to my small studio?
I haven't had a job since I graduated.
My partner has been supporting me.
He works from dawn to dusk.
I feel bad for him.
I want to... help share his burden.
I see.
But the pay here isn't high.
Oh, that's fine, really.
In that case, why don't you do a quick sketch?
I'll take a look at your fundamentals.
What's wrong? Is it hard for you to do it?
Well...
I injured my hand a while ago.
Oh, it's okay.
Just a simple sketch will do.
I just need to see the basics.
We only teach kids here.
As long as you're decent, it's fine.
Shen Mo, what's going on?
Since I injured my hand,
I haven't been able to hold a pen.
You can't hold it at all?
I've tried many times.
It's not working.
How long until it heals?
I don't know.
Oh dear.
Then there's nothing I can do.
If you can't draw,
I can't hire you even if I want to.
Sir, please don't worry.
I have the training and ability for this.
Whether you want me to teach or draw...
I can teach anything.
I can do anything.
I believe in your professional skills.
I believe in your teaching ability, too.
But you can't draw right now.
What if the kids need a demonstration?
I can't tell the kids that their teacher can't draw.
That just wouldn't work.
I've already sent out many resumes.
Please, sir.
I'm really sorry.
There's nothing I can do.
You should get your hand treated first.
How about this?
Call me when your hand gets better.
Okay.
Thank you, sir.
[Urgent Recruitment: Library Staff, Book Organization]
Shen Mo!
Mr. Ji, we found him.
Good.
Xiao Shen.
Work faster.
You're young, after all.
Yes, sir. I understand.
Shen Mo.
What are you doing here?
I got a job as a book organizer in the library.
It's my first day of trial work.
Why didn't you tell me you were going out?
Huh?
You didn't think I disappeared, did you?
You've been looking for me?
You haven't recovered yet.
What if something happened while you were out?
Oh, come on.
I'm fine.
How could I ever bear to leave you?
Why did you want to do this?
I just wanted to...
help out with the household expenses.
Dummy.
We don't need you to do this.
Does this go here?
Oh, yes.
These... These are all my tasks.
I can do it myself.
My boss is watching.
Let me do it.
Go home and wait for me.
- Okay. - Don't worry.
Okay.
- Bye-bye. - Bye.
You're off work early today.
How was it?
Was work tiring today?
It was okay.
You don't have to work this weekend, right?
No. Why?
Do you want to go to an art exhibition this weekend?
A friend of mine just gave me two tickets.
Wow!
Did your friend really give them to you?
Or did you know I wanted to go
and specifically asked for them?
Just tell me if you're going or not.
I'll go!
As long as I'm with you, I'll go anywhere.
Look at this.
Wow.
Look at the paintings by those masters.
They're really incredible.
I've seen your work.
You paint very well, too.
How can I compare to them?
You should quit your job at the library.
Why?
Have you ever seen a master working in a library?
Suffering can be a breeding ground for creativity.
I won't let you suffer again.
Once your hand is healed, keep painting.
Until you're better than all of them.
When I become a great painter and start making money,
I'll buy you that big house over there.
Okay.
I'll hold my exhibition here then.
And you can wait for me at home.
Okay.
I'll wait for you to come home.
All contract documents for this batch
strictly follow the Group's three-level audit process.
First, the head of the Business Department conducts a preliminary review
to verify data and project feasibility.
Then, the deputy general manager reviews and confirms it
to manage project and financial risks.
Finally, the Legal Department
and Risk Management Department perform a compliance check for...
Mr. Ji?
Is there something wrong with my proposal?
No, not at all.
Let's proceed with your proposal.
Meeting adjourned.
Mr. Ji, I was just about to get your signature.
I'm busy. Another day.
I'm going to the hospital.
Oh? Are you sick?
I'm not sick.
I'm visiting a patient.
I've never seen Mr. Ji like this.
Yeah.
It feels like he's in love.
Don't worry about that.
I've contacted the best hospital and specialists here.
This hand recovery surgery of yours...
will definitely be fine.
Yeah.
What if it can't be healed?
What if the surgery fails...
and it gets even worse?
Don't be afraid.
It will definitely be fine.
No matter what happens, I'll be by your side.
I was just kidding.
I'm not afraid.
It's great if it's healed,
but it's no big deal if it fails.
Besides, as long as you're by my side,
I'm not afraid of anything.
Sometimes, I really can't figure you out.
Huh?
You're so mild, anyone could bully you.
But once you get stubborn,
you're stubborn as a mule.
Is that a compliment or an insult?
- What do you think? - All right, don't be too nervous.
The surgery will be over by this time tomorrow.
It's nothing.
I just don't like hospitals much.
My mother...
Yeah?
Let's talk about that later.
Get some rest today.
The surgery is tomorrow.
[Operation]
Doctor, how is he?
Was the surgery successful?
It was very successful.
Hang in there.
The surgery was a success.
You'll be discharged soon.
I thought about it before the anesthesia.
If the surgery had failed,
I would've just let you be my right hand.
Don't talk like that.
Once you're discharged,
I'll take you out for a great meal.
Okay.
Wow, so many dishes!
They all look delicious.
Of course. This is my favorite hidden gem.
I don't usually bring people here.
It's such a nice place.
Who have you been bringing here?
Zhou Yang, Zhou Yang...
You'd better be honest with me.
I have something to discuss with you.
From today on, you'll live with me.
I've already found a place.
Why?
Isn't our current home fine?
You'll like our new home even more.
Where exactly is our new home?
Here?
Isn't this...
Yes.
To help you become a great artist sooner,
we should live closer to the art gallery.
But... this must be so expensive.
It's such a high-end neighborhood.
And didn't we say that I was going to give the house?
Think of it as an investment.
You're a future master artist.
All right.
Then for my comeback piece as the great artist Shen,
I'll paint you first, okay?
Or maybe a Ferris wheel.
A Ferris wheel?
Yeah.
Near your old rental place,
wasn't there a big Ferris wheel?
That was where I managed to win you over.
Don't move.
Your hand hasn't fully healed yet.
Thank you so much.
Did you forget something?
What?
Give me your hand.
Zhou Yang...
Do you think my hand can heal?
Of course.
As long as you persevere,
it will definitely pay off.
I'm sure of it.
Okay.
When my hand is healed,
I'm going to turn that empty, south-facing room
into a studio.
Then, I'll fill it with all my paintings.
And that painting...
The Ferris wheel will be right in the center.
That way, you'll see it immediately.
All right.
I'll paint at home then.
I'll cook for you at home,
and I can sing for you.
We can plan our trips together.
And also...
I must find a chance to devour you.
Merry Christmas.
During the New Year,
I plan to go abroad to be with my family.
Okay, that's great.
I'll just wait for you to come back.
What about you?
Will you be home alone during the New Year?
Or are you going back to your hometown?
It's fine. I'll just go back to my hometown.
Don't worry about me.
Merry Christmas!
I miss you.
Stop it.
Zhou Yang.
I'm not Zhou Yang.
You're the one I love most.
How could I be mistaken?
You're still not well.
I'm not sick at all.
We'll talk when you're better.
Hello?
What are you doing?
I'm...
I'm cleaning the house.
Aren't you going back to your hometown?
It's nearby.
I'll leave after I finish cleaning.
Oh, Zhou Yang, don't worry about me.
Just enjoy your time with your family abroad.
Okay.
Remember to apply the medicine on your hand.
Don't worry.
Okay, bye.
That was close.
Are you asleep?
Not yet.
I'm waiting for midnight.
What about you?
I'm still having dinner.
Oh, right.
There's a time difference.
Is celebrating New Year's abroad fun?
It's not that interesting.
Shen Mo.
Where are you right now?
I'm at home.
Are you alone?
I went back to my hometown.
My parents are both here.
Shen Mo.
Happy New Year.
Zhou Yang.
What are you doing right now?